{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213607650","data":{"timestamp":" 947213607649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213609784","data":{"timestamp":" 947213609783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213611913","data":{"timestamp":" 947213611912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213615120","data":{"timestamp":" 947213615119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213617397","data":{"timestamp":" 947213617396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213619651","data":{"timestamp":" 947213619650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213622506","data":{"timestamp":" 947213622505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213624672","data":{"timestamp":" 947213624671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213626917","data":{"timestamp":" 947213626916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213630167","data":{"timestamp":" 947213630167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213632288","data":{"timestamp":" 947213632288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213634408","data":{"timestamp":" 947213634407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213637389","data":{"timestamp":" 947213637388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213639657","data":{"timestamp":" 947213639656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213641939","data":{"timestamp":" 947213641939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213645007","data":{"timestamp":" 947213645006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213647336","data":{"timestamp":" 947213647335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213649689","data":{"timestamp":" 947213649688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213652742","data":{"timestamp":" 947213652742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213654901","data":{"timestamp":" 947213654900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213657084","data":{"timestamp":" 947213657083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213660275","data":{"timestamp":" 947213660274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213662498","data":{"timestamp":" 947213662497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213664712","data":{"timestamp":" 947213664711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213667899","data":{"timestamp":" 947213667899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213670326","data":{"timestamp":" 947213670325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213672735","data":{"timestamp":" 947213672734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213675860","data":{"timestamp":" 947213675859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213678170","data":{"timestamp":" 947213678169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213680472","data":{"timestamp":" 947213680472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213683476","data":{"timestamp":" 947213683475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213685710","data":{"timestamp":" 947213685710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213687964","data":{"timestamp":" 947213687963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213690953","data":{"timestamp":" 947213690952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213693319","data":{"timestamp":" 947213693318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213695662","data":{"timestamp":" 947213695661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213698781","data":{"timestamp":" 947213698780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213701144","data":{"timestamp":" 947213701143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213703561","data":{"timestamp":" 947213703560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213706559","data":{"timestamp":" 947213706558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213708853","data":{"timestamp":" 947213708852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213711183","data":{"timestamp":" 947213711182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213714447","data":{"timestamp":" 947213714446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213716693","data":{"timestamp":" 947213716692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213718986","data":{"timestamp":" 947213718984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213722352","data":{"timestamp":" 947213722352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213724813","data":{"timestamp":" 947213724812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213727288","data":{"timestamp":" 947213727287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213730155","data":{"timestamp":" 947213730154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213732352","data":{"timestamp":" 947213732351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213734515","data":{"timestamp":" 947213734514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213737936","data":{"timestamp":" 947213737935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213740256","data":{"timestamp":" 947213740255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213742607","data":{"timestamp":" 947213742606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213745715","data":{"timestamp":" 947213745715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213747995","data":{"timestamp":" 947213747995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213750287","data":{"timestamp":" 947213750286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213753320","data":{"timestamp":" 947213753319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213755489","data":{"timestamp":" 947213755488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213757662","data":{"timestamp":" 947213757660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213760816","data":{"timestamp":" 947213760815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213763065","data":{"timestamp":" 947213763064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213765331","data":{"timestamp":" 947213765330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213768604","data":{"timestamp":" 947213768603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213770839","data":{"timestamp":" 947213770838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213773064","data":{"timestamp":" 947213773063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213776335","data":{"timestamp":" 947213776333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213778644","data":{"timestamp":" 947213778643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213780999","data":{"timestamp":" 947213780998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213784097","data":{"timestamp":" 947213784096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213786438","data":{"timestamp":" 947213786438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213788788","data":{"timestamp":" 947213788786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213792200","data":{"timestamp":" 947213792198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213792336","data":{"timestamp":" 947213792336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 435286c6-6ee6-4418-8502-347d85c09b8c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213815647","data":{"timestamp":" 947213815647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213816035","data":{"timestamp":" 947213816034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213816535","data":{"timestamp":" 947213816535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213816891","data":{"timestamp":" 947213816890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213817314","data":{"timestamp":" 947213817313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213817800","data":{"timestamp":" 947213817799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213818034","data":{"timestamp":" 947213818034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213821220","data":{"timestamp":" 947213821219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213821259","data":{"timestamp":" 947213821258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213821982","data":{"timestamp":" 947213821982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213822394","data":{"timestamp":" 947213822393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213822703","data":{"timestamp":" 947213822702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213822922","data":{"timestamp":" 947213822921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213823130","data":{"timestamp":" 947213823129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213823464","data":{"timestamp":" 947213823464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213823700","data":{"timestamp":" 947213823699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213826887","data":{"timestamp":" 947213826886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213827300","data":{"timestamp":" 947213827299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213829913","data":{"timestamp":" 947213829913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213830128","data":{"timestamp":" 947213830127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213830341","data":{"timestamp":" 947213830341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213833873","data":{"timestamp":" 947213833872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213837663","data":{"timestamp":" 947213837662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213838697","data":{"timestamp":" 947213838697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213841455","data":{"timestamp":" 947213841455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213841843","data":{"timestamp":" 947213841843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213842339","data":{"timestamp":" 947213842338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213842694","data":{"timestamp":" 947213842693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213843108","data":{"timestamp":" 947213843108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213843594","data":{"timestamp":" 947213843593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213843829","data":{"timestamp":" 947213843828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213847046","data":{"timestamp":" 947213847045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213847081","data":{"timestamp":" 947213847081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213847807","data":{"timestamp":" 947213847806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213848216","data":{"timestamp":" 947213848215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213848522","data":{"timestamp":" 947213848521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213848741","data":{"timestamp":" 947213848741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213848949","data":{"timestamp":" 947213848948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213849276","data":{"timestamp":" 947213849275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213849512","data":{"timestamp":" 947213849512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213852161","data":{"timestamp":" 947213852160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213852284","data":{"timestamp":" 947213852284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" bc533f07-9e95-46fe-a737-50f7d349bf3d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213878881","data":{"timestamp":" 947213878880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213882257","data":{"timestamp":" 947213882257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213883844","data":{"timestamp":" 947213883844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213892916","data":{"timestamp":" 947213892915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213894531","data":{"timestamp":" 947213894530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213897459","data":{"timestamp":" 947213897458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213899067","data":{"timestamp":" 947213899066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213901598","data":{"timestamp":" 947213901597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213903237","data":{"timestamp":" 947213903236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213905973","data":{"timestamp":" 947213905972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213907591","data":{"timestamp":" 947213907590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213910130","data":{"timestamp":" 947213910130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213911732","data":{"timestamp":" 947213911731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213914477","data":{"timestamp":" 947213914476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" START_BAISIKELI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213918492","data":{"timestamp":" 947213918491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213920074","data":{"timestamp":" 947213920073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213927158","data":{"timestamp":" 947213927157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213928803","data":{"timestamp":" 947213928803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213931609","data":{"timestamp":" 947213931608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213933248","data":{"timestamp":" 947213933247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213936013","data":{"timestamp":" 947213936013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213937617","data":{"timestamp":" 947213937617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213940066","data":{"timestamp":" 947213940066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213941665","data":{"timestamp":" 947213941664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213944492","data":{"timestamp":" 947213944492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213946124","data":{"timestamp":" 947213946123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213949002","data":{"timestamp":" 947213949001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213951026","data":{"timestamp":" 947213951024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213951120","data":{"timestamp":" 947213951120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" db241062-243b-4a47-b530-15d91c669110"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213965529","data":{"timestamp":" 947213965528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213973428","data":{"timestamp":" 947213973427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213975041","data":{"timestamp":" 947213975040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213978186","data":{"timestamp":" 947213978186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213979765","data":{"timestamp":" 947213979764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213982550","data":{"timestamp":" 947213982550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213984178","data":{"timestamp":" 947213984177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213986827","data":{"timestamp":" 947213986827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213988466","data":{"timestamp":" 947213988465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213991378","data":{"timestamp":" 947213991377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213992991","data":{"timestamp":" 947213992990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213995684","data":{"timestamp":" 947213995684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947213997311","data":{"timestamp":" 947213997310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214000052","data":{"timestamp":" 947214000051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" START_BAISIKELI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214004859","data":{"timestamp":" 947214004858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214006485","data":{"timestamp":" 947214006483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214009297","data":{"timestamp":" 947214009296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214010888","data":{"timestamp":" 947214010888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214013660","data":{"timestamp":" 947214013660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214015279","data":{"timestamp":" 947214015279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214017932","data":{"timestamp":" 947214017932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214019601","data":{"timestamp":" 947214019600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214022344","data":{"timestamp":" 947214022344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214023951","data":{"timestamp":" 947214023950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214026659","data":{"timestamp":" 947214026659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214028276","data":{"timestamp":" 947214028275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214031154","data":{"timestamp":" 947214031153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214032757","data":{"timestamp":" 947214032755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214035419","data":{"timestamp":" 947214035418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214037443","data":{"timestamp":" 947214037441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214037545","data":{"timestamp":" 947214037545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9740595e-8812-4553-aae2-fe26911046e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBO"," userResponse":" BIBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214062142","data":{"timestamp":" 947214062141"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_v-a-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214065498","data":{"timestamp":" 947214065498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_k-b-n"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214068963","data":{"timestamp":" 947214068963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_w-r-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214072225","data":{"timestamp":" 947214072225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_v-b-r"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214075448","data":{"timestamp":" 947214075447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_e-b-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214079287","data":{"timestamp":" 947214079287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-h"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214082787","data":{"timestamp":" 947214082787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_o-d-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214086212","data":{"timestamp":" 947214086212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-s-r"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214089526","data":{"timestamp":" 947214089525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-ch-w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214093529","data":{"timestamp":" 947214093529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214099336","data":{"timestamp":" 947214099335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" b79bf7e3-5c07-4ea2-be8c-365fade3d201"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.show.80"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-w"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214121604","data":{"timestamp":" 947214121604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214124805","data":{"timestamp":" 947214124805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214128138","data":{"timestamp":" 947214128137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_z-b-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214131578","data":{"timestamp":" 947214131577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_i-b-f"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214135561","data":{"timestamp":" 947214135560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214139158","data":{"timestamp":" 947214139157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214145354","data":{"timestamp":" 947214145353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214149449","data":{"timestamp":" 947214149448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-y-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214153410","data":{"timestamp":" 947214153409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-ch-m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214157082","data":{"timestamp":" 947214157081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214162948","data":{"timestamp":" 947214162946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" d20684b4-7449-4e36-804b-e5f207328762"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214193590","data":{"timestamp":" 947214193590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214200451","data":{"timestamp":" 947214200451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214207292","data":{"timestamp":" 947214207291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214214136","data":{"timestamp":" 947214214136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214220976","data":{"timestamp":" 947214220976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214227803","data":{"timestamp":" 947214227802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214235489","data":{"timestamp":" 947214235489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214242310","data":{"timestamp":" 947214242309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214249164","data":{"timestamp":" 947214249162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214255988","data":{"timestamp":" 947214255986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214262929","data":{"timestamp":" 947214262927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214275223","data":{"timestamp":" 947214275221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 64b91e6c-271f-447a-b080-807466e1c874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214296645","data":{"timestamp":" 947214296644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214297710","data":{"timestamp":" 947214297709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214304371","data":{"timestamp":" 947214304370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214305461","data":{"timestamp":" 947214305460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214308554","data":{"timestamp":" 947214308554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214309624","data":{"timestamp":" 947214309624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214310507","data":{"timestamp":" 947214310506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214310724","data":{"timestamp":" 947214310724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214330765","data":{"timestamp":" 947214330762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214378702","data":{"timestamp":" 947214378699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" ff7b4f6c-14fb-4fc8-8dc1-43d6b6fd3a3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214424456","data":{"timestamp":" 947214424454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214430003","data":{"timestamp":" 947214429998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214435161","data":{"timestamp":" 947214435158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214440165","data":{"timestamp":" 947214440163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214445903","data":{"timestamp":" 947214445900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214451596","data":{"timestamp":" 947214451594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214457397","data":{"timestamp":" 947214457395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214462958","data":{"timestamp":" 947214462953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214468104","data":{"timestamp":" 947214468101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214473605","data":{"timestamp":" 947214473603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214480819","data":{"timestamp":" 947214480817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214486607","data":{"timestamp":" 947214486595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214493060","data":{"timestamp":" 947214493058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214498985","data":{"timestamp":" 947214498983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214504049","data":{"timestamp":" 947214504043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214509216","data":{"timestamp":" 947214509214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214518136","data":{"timestamp":" 947214518134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214524613","data":{"timestamp":" 947214524611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214530561","data":{"timestamp":" 947214530558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214536096","data":{"timestamp":" 947214536094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214543330","data":{"timestamp":" 947214543328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214549232","data":{"timestamp":" 947214549227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214556809","data":{"timestamp":" 947214556806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214565925","data":{"timestamp":" 947214565922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947214573517","data":{"timestamp":" 947214573503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_055311"," gameId":" 9fa1e2a6-9966-43b6-8777-f5d2bf62a717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}